Guide to the Rice University Dean of Architecture Search Committee records, 1988-1993 UA 047
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Dean of Architecture Search Committee records
1988-1993
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 047
1.5 Linear Feet (3 boxes)
Records of the Search Committee for the position of Dean of Architecture, spanning the years 1988 to 1993.
Scope and Contents
Records of the Search Committee for the position of Dean of Architecture, spanning the years 1988 to 1993. Included are committee material from committees of 1988, 1990, and 1992-93, and files of candidates for 1989, 1990 and related correspondence.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
This material requires special permission for access. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 for assistance.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
letters (correspondence)
- Committee, 1988; 150221 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Forbes, Peter, 150222 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Committee, 1989; 150223 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Candidates, 1989; 150224
  - Clark, W.G., 150243 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dennis, Michael, 150244 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dunster, David, 150245 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fraker, Harrison, 150246 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Halsband, Francis, 150247 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Holl, Steven, 150248 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Edward, 150249 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lerup, Lars, 150250 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - McMinn, William G., 150251 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Moss, Eric O., 150252 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Plater-Zyberk, Elizabeth, 150253 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Polyzoldes, Stefanos, 150254 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rotondi, Michael, 150255 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Seligmann, Werner, 150256 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Wolin, Judith, 150257 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Committee, 1990; 150225 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Candidates, 1990; 150226
  - Amico, Robert L., 150227 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - De La Fuente, Guillaume Julian, 150228 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fredenburgh, Harold, 150229 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Keating, Richard, 150230 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lizon, Peter, 150231 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meder, John, 150232 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pearson, Paul D., 150233 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pierce, Gifford, 150234 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Shirvani, Hamid, 150235 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Tzonis, Alexander, 150236 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Committee, 1991; 150237 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Student Questionnaire, 1992; 150238 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Reviews, 1992; 150239 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1992; 150240 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Committee, 1992; 150241 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
- Committee, 1992-93; 150242 (Box 3, Folder 4)